swiftway.net 2010-12-08

# SwiftWay: Privacy Statement

Last Modified Februari 18th, 2008

**Privacy Statement**

The Information We Obtain and How We Use It 

The information we obtain from you is generally necessary for us to provide you with services and design new services for your future use. For example, we need to know your company name, address and the services you buy from us to properly provide and invoice for those services or recommend how we can best serve you.

We may also use information in our records to protect our customers, employees or property - for instance, to investigate fraud, harassment or other types of unlawful service activities involving Swiftway or other carriers that we do business with. In some cases, it may be necessary to provide this information to the government or third parties that make a lawful demand for it.

We share information within our Swiftway companies to enable us to better understand our customers' product and service needs, and to learn how to best design, develop, and package products and services to best meet those needs. Like any large business, we have structured our company to include a number of smaller companies.

**Accuracy of the Information We Hold**

We want to make sure the information we obtain and use about customers is accurate. To that end, we strive to verify that our customer records are correct. Much of this information is reflected in your monthly invoice. Furthermore you may view your records upon request. If you see an inaccuracy on your Swiftway invoice or in your records, and you let us know, we can correct it.

**Security and Accountability  **

We have information systems that collect and store customer information in addition to systems that store our own business records. These systems have different types of security as appropriate for the information stored. Swiftway requires employees to keep customer information confidential and we hold them accountable for their actions.

**Disclosure of Information Outside Swiftway  **

As a general rule, without your permission, Swiftway does not release confidential customer information to unaffiliated third parties unless we have a business relationship with those companies where the disclosure is appropriate. For example, we may hire outside companies as contractors or agents; or we might be engaged in a joint venture or partnership with a company. We provide information to these other companies only as needed to accomplish our business objectives and the companies are bound by requirements to keep Swiftway customers' information confidential. 

There are exceptions to the general rule. For example, we might provide information to regulatory or administrative agencies so that they can accomplish their regulatory tasks or to maximise the efficiencies of our own processes. Other disclosures will be driven by legal requirements imposed on Swiftway. Swiftway complies with "legal process," such as a subpoena or court order or other similar demand, associated with either criminal or civil proceedings; and, if not prohibited by the legal document, we will advise you of the demand.

**Privacy Over the Internet**

The only individually identifiable information Swiftway obtains about individual visitors to our Web sites is information supplied voluntarily by the visitor. This means that you can visit our Web sites without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. To gauge the effectiveness of our Web sites, we do collect some non-individually-identifiable generic information about our visitors. Our Web servers automatically recognise a visitor's Internet service provider, the IP address, the domain name, the type of browser, and the operating system. In addition to, which pages are viewed on our sites, the Web page you were on when you link to our sites, how much time a visitor spends on each page and other information related to the operation and interaction of Swiftway Web sites. This information does not reveal a visitor's identity. We aggregate this information and use it to evaluate and improve our Web sites. 

You can choose to provide individually identifiable information to Swiftway in a number of ways through our Web sites - by ordering a service from us, sending us email, registering to receive news or information or applying for a job. When visitors supply information about themselves for a specific purpose, Swiftway uses the information for that purpose (such as to provide the information the visitor has requested or to consider a visitor for a particular job). In addition, when visitors use our Web sites to order services, or to request information about our services, we may use the individually identifiable information as we would use the same information obtained off-line - for example, to evaluate your service needs and contact you regarding additional services you may find useful.

We do not sell or disclose individually identifiable information obtained on-line about our visitors, to anyone outside of Swiftway except as described above (when Swiftway is in a business relationship with an unaffiliated party and then under confidentiality restrictions) unless you specifically authorise it, it is required by law (including the service of subpoenas or court orders in either civil or criminal lawsuits), or disclosure is necessary to protect the safety of customers, employees or property. If you provide individually identifiable information to us in the context of an event Swiftway sponsors with another company, such as a contest, or if you register on a co-sponsored site or feature, you may also be providing the individually identifiable information to the co-sponsor.

The Swiftway Web sites may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by other sites. Other Web sites may have different privacy policies or no policy. Users should review the privacy policies of any Web site before providing personal information.

**E-Mail Communications:**

Swiftway, or those with whom Swiftway has a business relationship, will use email to communicate with our customers, respond to visitors' emails, or to inform about events or new products. If you do not want to receive emails about events or new products from Swiftway and/or those with whom Swiftway has a business relationship you can object thereto. 

* * *

**Update of this Privacy Statement**

To improve the services it can offer you, Swiftway may opt to expand its capabilities for obtaining information about users in the future. Swiftway will update this privacy statement continually to ensure that you are aware of developments in this area.

Swiftway is committed to maintaining the privacy of customer information. At Swiftway, your privacy is a priority. 

_Swiftway is committed to maintaining the privacy of customer information. At Swiftway, your privacy is a priority. We can be reached via e-mail at[support@swiftway.co.uk](mailto:support@swiftway.co.uk) for all questions related to this Privacy Statement or any other privacy-related matter._
